Guide to the National Education Association-Conventions records, 1857-1998 NEA1008.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conventions and Conferences, Bulk, 1970-1996 1858-1998; 1970-1996; Series 1; National Education Association of the United States. Meeting.; 85 Linear Feet
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Convention Bureau-Promotional, 1983; Series 1 (Box 1374, Folder 10)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Convention Hall-Contracts, 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 1374, Folder 11)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Convention Schedule, Series 1 (Box 1374, Folder 12)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Correspondence-Director/OCCM, 1983; Series 1 (Box 1374, Folder 13)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 1374, Folder 14)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Delegate Mailings [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1374, Folder 15)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Delegate Mailings [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1375, Folder 1)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Delegate Material-Representative Assembly, Series 1 (Box 1375, Folder 2)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Delegate Seating, Series 1 (Box 1375, Folder 3)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Drivers, Series 1 (Box 1375, Folder 4)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Evaluations, Series 1 (Box 1375, Folder 5)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Exhibits [file 1/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1375, Folder 6)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Exhibits [file 2/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1375, Folder 7)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Exhibits [file 3/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1375, Folder 8)
    Contains 2 photos.
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Exhibits [file 4/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1376, Folder 1)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-First Aid, Series 1 (Box 1376, Folder 2)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Floor Plans [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1376, Folder 3)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Floor Plans [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1376, Folder 4)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Food Service, Series 1 (Box 1376, Folder 5)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Friendship Night, Series 1 (Box 1377, Folder 1)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Furniture/Equipment Orders, Series 1 (Box 1377, Folder 2)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Host Committee [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1377, Folder 3)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Host Committee [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1377, Folder 4)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Hotel-General, 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 1377, Folder 5)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Hotel-Pickups, Series 1 (Box 1377, Folder 6)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Magazine [file 1/3], Series 1 (Box 1377, Folder 7)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Magazine [file 2/3], Series 1 (Box 1377, Folder 8)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Magazine [file 3/3], Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 1)
    Contains 5 photos.
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Maps, Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 2)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Miscellaneous [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 3)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Miscellaneous [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 4)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Programs, Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 5)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Restaurant Survey, Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 6)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Security, Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 7)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Social Events, Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 8)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Staff Assignments, Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 9)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Staff Dates/Housing, Series 1 (Box 1378, Folder 10)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-State Coordinators [file 1/3], 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 1379, Folder 1)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-State Coordinators [file 2/3], 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 1379, Folder 2)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-State Coordinators [file 3/3], 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 1379, Folder 3)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Telephone Directory, Series 1 (Box 1379, Folder 4)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Telephone Orders, Series 1 (Box 1379, Folder 5)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-Transportation Tours, Series 1 (Box 1379, Folder 6)
  - 1984-Minneapolis, MN-TV Sound, Series 1 (Box 1379, Folder 7)
  - 1984: Quality Reforms in Education: Coordinated State Staff Conference, February 1984; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 20)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Bills, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Budget, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Building Tours, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Busing, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Camping, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Candidates, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Car Rental, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Caucuses-Minority, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 8)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Caucuses-State, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 9)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Childcare, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 10)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Convention Bureau-Correspondence, 1983-1985; Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 11)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Convention Hall Contracts, Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 12)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Convention Hall Correspondence, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 1380, Folder 13)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Convention Schedule, Series 1 (Box 1381, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Correspondence-Miscellaneous [file 1/3], Series 1 (Box 1381, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Correspondence-Miscellaneous [file 2/3], Series 1 (Box 1381, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Correspondence-Miscellaneous [file 3/3], Series 1 (Box 1381, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Delegate Material-Mailings [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1381, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Delegate Material-Mailings [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1382, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Delegate Seating, Series 1 (Box 1382, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Drivers [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1382, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Drivers [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1382, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Evaluation, Series 1 (Box 1382, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Exhibits [file 1/5], Series 1 (Box 1382, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Exhibits [file 2/5], Series 1 (Box 1383, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Exhibits [file 3/5], Series 1 (Box 1383, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Exhibits [file 4/5], Series 1 (Box 1383, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Exhibits [file 5/5], Series 1 (Box 1383, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-First Aid, Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Floor Plans, Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Floor Privilege, Ribbon Guide, Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Food Service, Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Friendship Night, Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Furniture and Equipment Orders, Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Host Committee [file 1/3], Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Host Committee [file 2/3], Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 8)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Host Committee [file 3/3], Series 1 (Box 1384, Folder 9)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotel Committments, Series 1 (Box 1385, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Additional Hotels, Series 1 (Box 1385, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Capital Hilton, Series 1 (Box 1385, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Convention Center Inn, Series 1 (Box 1385, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Executive House, Series 1 (Box 1385, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-General [file 1/3], Series 1 (Box 1385, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-General [file 2/3], Series 1 (Box 1385, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-General [file 3/3], Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Georgetown Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Governor's House, Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Gramercy Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Highland Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Holiday Inn, Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Holiday Inn Capitol, Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Holiday Inn Central, Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 8)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Hyatt Regency, Series 1 (Box 1386, Folder 9)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-L'Enfant Plaza, Series 1 (Box 1387, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Quality Inn Capitol Hill, Series 1 (Box 1387, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Quality Inn Downtown, Series 1 (Box 1387, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Quality Inn-Embassy Suites [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1387, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Quality Inn-Embassy Suites [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1387, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Ramada Inn Central, Series 1 (Box 1387, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Sheraton Carlton, Series 1 (Box 1387, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Sheraton Grand, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1387, Folder 8)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Sheraton Washington, Series 1 (Box 1388, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Shoreham, Series 1 (Box 1388, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Washington Hilton, Series 1 (Box 1388, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Washington Hotel, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1388, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Washington Marriot, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1388, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Hotels-Washington Plaza, Series 1 (Box 1388, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-IPD-Showcase Exhibit, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1388, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Magazine [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1389, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Magazine [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1389, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Maps, Series 1 (Box 1389, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Miscellaneous [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1389, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Miscellaneous [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1389, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-New Business Items, Series 1 (Box 1390, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Non-Profit, Series 1 (Box 1390, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Parking, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1390, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Physically Handicapped, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1390, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Restaurant Survey, Series 1 (Box 1390, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Security, Series 1 (Box 1390, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Shipping, Series 1 (Box 1390, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Social Events, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1390, Folder 8)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Special Convention Committee, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Staff Appointments, Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Staff Dates, Staff Housing, Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-State Coordinators [file 1/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-State Coordinators [file 2/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-State Coordinators [file 3/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-State Coordinators [file 4/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-State Housing Adjustment Points [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 8)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-State Housing Adjustment Points [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1391, Folder 9)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-State Housing Lists, Series 1 (Box 1392, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Telephone Directory, Series 1 (Box 1392, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Telephone Orders, Series 1 (Box 1392, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation [file 1/7], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1392, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation [file 2/7], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1392, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation [file 3/7], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1392, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation [file 4/7], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1392, Folder 7)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation [file 5/7], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1393, Folder 1)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation [file 6/7], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1393, Folder 2)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation [file 7/7], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1393, Folder 3)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation-Tours [file 1/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1393, Folder 4)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation-Tours [file 2/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1393, Folder 5)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation-Tours [file 3/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1393, Folder 6)
  - 1985-Washington, DC-Transportation-Tours [file 4/4], 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1393, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Bills, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Blood Donor, Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Budget, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Busing, Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Camping, Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Candidates, Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Car Rental Information, Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Caucuses-Special Interest, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Caucuses-State, Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Check Cashing Policy, Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 10)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Child Care, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 11)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Convention Bureau Correspondence, 1981-1988; Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 12)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Convention Bureau Promotional, 1982-1986; Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 13)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Convention Hall-Contracts, 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 1394, Folder 14)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Convention Hall-Correspondence [file 1/2], 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Convention Hall-Correspondence [file 2/2], 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Convention Schedule, Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Convention and Tourism Bureau, Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Correspondence, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Correspondence-Director to OCCM, Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Delegate Material, Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Delegate Material-Representative Assembly [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Delegate Material-Representative Assembly [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1395, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Delegate Seating, Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Drivers, Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Evaluations, Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Exhibits [file 1/4], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Exhibits [file 2/4], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Exhibits [file 3/4], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Exhibits [file 4/4], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-First Aid, Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Floor Plans, Series 1 (Box 1396, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Floor Privledge/Ribbon Guide, Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Food Service, Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Friendship Night, Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Host Committee [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Host Committee [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Admiral BenBow, Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Best Western-Admirals Inn, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Best Western-Greentree Inn, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Best Western-Midtown, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Breckinridge Inn, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 1397, Folder 10)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Brock's Residence Inn, Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-The Brown, Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Brownsboro/Ramada East, 1984-1985; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Colonial Inn, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Continental Inn, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Days Inn-Jeffersonville, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Days Inn-Sellersburg, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Econolodge, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Executive Inn, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Executive West, 1983-1984; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 10)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Executive West Motor Hotel, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 11)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Galt House, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1398, Folder 12)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-General [file 1/2], 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-General [file 2/2], 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Hilton Inn, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Airport East, Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Airport South, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Central, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Downtown, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Midtown, Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-New Albany, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-North, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 10)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Northeast, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 11)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Northwest, Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 12)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Rivermont, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 13)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-South, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 14)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Southeast, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 15)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Southwest, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 16)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Howard Johnson-In Towne, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 17)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Howard Johnson Motor Lodge, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 18)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Hyatt Regency, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1399, Folder 19)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Hyatt Regency Louisville, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Knights Inn, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-La Quinta, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Louisville Inn, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Marriot Inn, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Motel Six, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Plaza East Inn, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Quality Inn-Jeffersonville, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Ramada Inn-Airport, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Ramada Inn-East, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 10)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Ramada Inn-Hurstbourne, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 11)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Red Carpet, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 12)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Red Roof Inn, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 13)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Red Roof Inn-Blairwood, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 14)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Red Roof Inn-Newburg, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 15)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Red Roof Inn-Preston, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 16)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Rodeway Inn [1/2], Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 17)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Rodeway Inn [2/2], Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 18)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Royce Inn, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 19)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Seelbach Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 20)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Sheraton Inn, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 21)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Sheraton Lakeview, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 22)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Skylight Inn, Series 1 (Box 1400, Folder 23)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Thrifty Dutchman, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Travelodge, Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Hotels-Travelodge of Louisville, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Information Booth [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Information Booth [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Magazines [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Magazines [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Maps, Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Miscellaneous [file 1/3], 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 1401, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Miscellaneous [file 2/3], 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 1402, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Miscellaneous [file 3/3], 1983-1986; Series 1 (Box 1402, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Non-Profit Affiliate Fund Raiser, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1402, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Parking, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1402, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Program, Series 1 (Box 1402, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Program Distribution, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1402, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Representative Assembly Social Events, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1402, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Restaurant, Series 1 (Box 1402, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Restaurant Survey, Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Security, Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Social Events, Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-State Coordinators [file 1/4], 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-State Coordinators [file 2/4], 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 5)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-State Coordinators [file 3/4], 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 6)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-State Coordinators [file 4/4], 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 7)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Staff Assignments, Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 8)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Staff Dates-Housing, Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 9)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-State Housing, Series 1 (Box 1403, Folder 10)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-State Housing-Selection Policy, Series 1 (Box 1404, Folder 1)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Telephone Directory, Series 1 (Box 1404, Folder 2)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Telephone Orders, Series 1 (Box 1404, Folder 3)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Tours/Special Events [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1404, Folder 4)
  - 1986-Louisville, KY-Tours/Special Events [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1404, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Administrative Office, Series 1 (Box 1404, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Annual Meeting Handouts [file 1/4], Series 1 (Box 1404, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Annual Meeting Handouts [file 2/4], Series 1 (Box 1404, Folder 8)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Annual Meeting Handouts [file 3/4], Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Annual Meeting Handouts [file 4/4], Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Band Opening Ceremony, Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Bills, Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Budget, Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Bureau and Center, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Busing, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Camping, Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 8)